earthables.com 2018-03-04

# Privacy Policy

COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Any information which is provided by you will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality and in accordance with the terms of the Data Protection Acts 1988 to 2003, Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24th October 1995 on the Protection of Individuals with regard to the Processing of Personal Data and on the Free Movement of such data, and any implementing and/or amending legislation as may be adopted in Ireland from time to time.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>   
CONTACT US ABOUT PRIVACY

We welcome any feedback on any privacy concern that you may have. We will use very effort to comply with this privacy policy and take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. earthables.com shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this privacy policy. earthables.com may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on earthables.com or protect and defend the rights and property of earthables.com and its products This privacy policy shall be governed by the laws of the Republic of U.S.
